天真冷
It's cold.
哦 真好 谢谢
Oh, good.Thank you.
冰淇淋店新来了个女孩儿
There's a new girl at/the ice cream store.
她好像不喜欢扣上衣纽扣
She doesn't seem too fond/of buttoning her top button.
我们去看看她
Let's go check her out.
我们在这儿干什么呢--都快四点了
what are we supposed to/be doing--it's almost 4:00.
你有别的地方去?
You got somewhere to be?
他喜欢操纵别人 说不定这就是考验
We know he likes to manipulate/people.He's probably testing us.
能考验出什么呢?
To find out what?
看我们能这样傻多久?
How long we can look stupid for?
他说三点前来 显然不会来了
He said he'd be here by 3:00./He's obviously not coming.
- 我要回家了/- 谁都别跟着她
- I'm going home./- nobody follow her.
她这招"我走了" 上周骗了九个人出局
She pied pipered nine people/right out of a job last week.
你能帮忙拿一下我的标志物么?
Would you mind holding/my metaphor for a second?
新病人 37岁的男性
New patient.37 year-old male.
严重的肌肉上行神经传导衰弱
Suffers from severe/ascending muscle weakness.
- 你为什么迟到?/- 看你们谁忍受不了
- Why are you late?/- To see who'd put up with it.
我们要是离开 就会被解雇?
So if we left,we would have been fired?
我本打算解雇坚守在此的/不过既然大家都在
I was gonna fire  whoever stuck/around.But since everyone stuck around...
脊柱28%的弧度会引起肺容量减少
28% curvature of the spine has/caused reduced lung capacity,
骨密度减少
and has reduced bone mineral density.
病人有脊髓性肌萎缩症
patient has spinal muscular atrophy.
遗传性的 无法治愈
It's genetic,incurable.
这不是一个诊断谜题
This is not  a diagnostic mystery.
- 你刚刚向敌方透漏了国家机密/- 什么敌方?
- You have just given state secrets to the enemy./- What enemy?
新病人 新规则 今天你们将分为两队
New patient. New rules. Today you're/gonna split yourselves into two teams.
病人虽患有SMA(脊髓性肌萎缩症)/但还有二十来年好活
First to figure out what's/threatening to deprive the patient
哪队先弄明白/现在是什么威胁了他的性命
of the 20 or so miserable/years he's got left with sma,
就能保住工作
gets to keep their jobs. .
拿掉编号吧 看起来很傻/我现在知道你们谁是谁了
Take off your numbers.You look stupid.And/I think I know who you are by now.
等等 你想让我们怎么分组?
Wait.How do you want us to split up?
好问题 过度兴奋的寄养小孩
Good question,overly/excited former foster kid.
你们有十个人 六个对六个怎么样?/哦 不对
There's ten of you. I'm thinking/six against six.No, wait.
- 男对女怎么样?/- 好建议 胖的那个双胞胎
- How about women versus men?/- Excellent suggestion,fat twin.
比偶数对奇数有趣 没衬衫对光膀子好玩
More interesting  than evens versus odds,less/interesting than shirts against skins.
如果你的生殖器官悬垂 就是联盟队的
If your sex organs/dangle,you're the confederates.
如果你的生殖器官赏心悦目/就是扬基队的
If your sex organs are aesthetically/pleasing,you're the yanks.
House医生... 我想参加男队
Dr. House... I'd like/to be on the men's team.
你的生殖器官悬垂吗 见血封喉的婆娘?
Do your sex organs/dangle, cutthroat bitch?
现在还不
Not yet.
你的团队里以前从没有超过一个女性成员
You've never hired more than/one female in your team before.
如果你非要肃清掉某个性别/那肯定不是男的
If you're going to purge  an entire/gender,it isn't going to be the danglers.
好像符合逻辑
Sounds logical.
如果只想三秒钟的话
If you don't think about it/for more than three seconds.
但我刚说过如果男队输了 他们就出局
But I just told you that if/the danglers lose, they're out.
所以我只能假设 你在隐瞒真正的原因
So I can only assume,you're/hiding the real reason.
你觉得女人积极性不足
You don't think the women/will be aggressive enough,
学术性不强 她们太感情用事了
or be good enough at/science,they'll be too emotional.
我能换队吗?
Can I switch teams?
- 如果男队同意 我没问题/- 我们不同意
- If the danglers are okay,I'm okay./- We're not okay.
我明白了 你不喜欢我是因为
I get it.You don't like me because
- 也许我有点好胜/- 你太老谋深算了
- maybe I'm a little bit competitive./- Manipulative.
见血封喉的婆娘是你的正式头衔
Cutthroat bitch is your official title.
这是个游戏 要玩得开心就甭想赢
It's a game.U can either/play for fun or play to win.
你们如果想赢 就得冷酷无情
If you want to win,you want cutthroat.
不 谢谢你
No, thank you.
第一件事就是要研究他的想法
First thing we have to do/is get inside his head.
这不是心理学问题
It's not psychological.
我不是在说病人 是说House
I'm not talking about the/patient, I'm talking about House.
他是疯了 但不至于没责任感
He's insane,but he's not irresponsible.
如果不是已经知道答案 他不会玩这游戏
He wouldn't be playing  this game,if/the didn't already know the answer.
首先 我们该一拥而上
First thing we do is/gang bang the sucker.
我们有五个人 可以做许多测试
There's five of us.We/can run dozens of tests.
我们不需要理论 只用蛮力就行了
We don't need a theory.We/just need brute force.
会不会是援助犬?
What about the assist dog?
用细菌滋生的嘴叼起布满细菌的东西
Picks bacteria-infested things up/with its bacteria-infested mouth,
- 交给那个人.../- 不是狗 太不公平了
- hands them over to the guy and.../- ithe dog.It wouldn't be fair.
- 对谁?/- 谁? 男队的人
- To who?/- Whom? The men.
House知道我以前是兽医
House knows I used to be a vet.
如果狗是答案 他们就处于弱势
If the dog's the/answer,they'd be at a handicap.
会不会是狗?
What about the dog?
援助犬什么都用嘴拿
Assist dogs put/everything  in their mouth,
- 钱 门把手/- 很好
- money, door knobs./- Great.
我说的不是那个 你为什么写下低钠...
That's not what I said.Why/do you think a low sodium...
不 是迷惑敌人
I don't
病人两周前去过泰国旅游
The patient took a trip to Thailand two weeks ago.
- 写大点 白板角度转一下 好让她们看到/- 不该这么做
- Hey,write bigger And angle the board more so they can see it./- This is wrong.
只有她们看了 这么做才不对/如果偷看我们 她们就不对
It's only wrong  Ty cheat f us And if/they cheat off us,They're wrong.
她们没有偷看 有个人行动了
They're not cheating.One/of them is moving.
嘿 别玩你的缝合线 不然就要重缝了
Hey,stop playing With your/sutures Or I'll have to redo them.
你们为什么把D号电池放在尿样杯里?
Why do you guys Keep a d cell/battery In a urine specimen cup?
因为它是从一个病人的肠道里取出来的
Because we pulled it From/a patient's intestine.
为什么会有人吞电池?
Why would somebody Swallow a battery?
这可不是吞下的?
Why do you assume It was swallowed?
五号床需要一袋乳酸林格氏液
Bed five needs a bag/Of ringer's lactate.
如果他用9伏特的电池 会更惨
It would have been worse/If he'd used a nine volt.
病人可不是男的?
Who said it was a "he"?
错误的假设 你很有一套/想让我像他一样思考
False assumptions.You're good.You're/trying to get me To think like him.
而你正在拍我马屁 为什么?
And you're trying To kiss my/ass.Why are you talking to me?
因为House正在把治病当作游戏
Because House is turning/Patient care into a game.
很危险... 病人会受罪 也许会死
It's dangerous... The patient's/gonna suffer,Maybe die.
哇 你该修面了
Wow,You really need to shave.
看我修得不错吧?
See what I did there?
呜哇
Whoa
有趣
Interesting.
来一辆急救车!
Need a crash cart in here!
我什么都没干
I didn't do it.
人们昏倒是因为脑供血不足
when a person faints,it's because They're/not getting Enough blood to their brain.
昏倒这个动作减缓供血不足
The act of falling Corrects the problem.
你昏倒在电动轮椅里 身体倒不下...
You faint again strapped Into that/power chair Where you can't fall...
你有可能醒不来
You might not wake up.
被辅助装备杀死
killed by an assistive device.
至少我的死很有讽刺意味
At least my death Would be ironic.
你在泰国时可能感染了粪圆属的线虫
I think when you Went to thailand You/picked up a thread worm Called strongyloides.
它们通常从脚进入人体
They usually go up Through your feet.
我没怎么在沙滩上散步
I didn't do a lot of/Walking on the beach.
但我估计你让别人把你平放在沙子上了
But I assume You did have/someone Lay you down in the sand.
光脊背和腿比光脚的接触机会大十倍
Bare back,bare legs.Increases/exposure Tenfold over bare feet.
两粒药
Two pills.
你就会好了
You'll be all better.
能帮我拿些水吃药吗?
Can I have some water For those,please?
- 嘿 排队等着吧/- House可没说要轮流
- Hey,take a number./- House didn't say anything About taking turns.
- 她在给他检查什么?/- 别说
- What's she testing him for?/- Don't.
他们会翻来覆去想我的理论/不去想新的
They'll spend all day obsessing over my idea/Instead of coming up With one of their own.
- 还有 我有可能是错的/- 说真的
- And hey,i might be wrong./- Seriously.
我担心如果不知道她给你吃了什么/会有药物冲突
I'm worried that  if we don't know What/she's giving you There can be conflicts.
不会的 House说他会掌握全局
No,you're not.House told me/He's keeping track Of all that.
十个医生 应该会有十种治疗
ten doctors.They should/be getting Ten cures.
我们需要血液 头发和粪便
We need blood,Hair,and stool.
你如厕后用木棒收集粪便
You poop,and then You use the wooden/sticks To collect the fecal matter,
涂在绿盒子上
Then you rub it On the green box.
交给我的狗吧/上述这些事 我能独自完成的只有一项
Hand it to my dog.only one of/those things  I can do on my own.
过去几天以来 我还没做过
And the last couple of days,I/haven't been doing that.
如果我们...抱你去洗手间 你不介意吧?
Is it all right With you if/we...Carry you into the bathroom?
如果你想要我去厕所 就得抱我去
If you want me there,That's the/way You're gonna have to do it.
- 准备好了?/- 嗯
- Okay.Ready?/- Mm-hm.
1 2 3
One,two,three.
能托一下我的头吗? 谢谢
Can I get a little Head/support,please?Thank you.
你来这儿干嘛?
Why are you here?
我的办公室被我的小分队们占用了
My offices are being used By my teams.
小分队"们"?
Teams?
就是说你只能在这里吼我了
Which means this is the only/Place where you can yell at me.
你有不止一个小分队?
You have teams?
两个 我今天愿意来听你吼
Two of them.I wanted to/deal With the yelling today,
是因为注意到你的穿着/听你吼多几句 都无所谓了
Because I noticed What you were wearing,And/i wouldn't have to listen All that closely.
你不能把医治病人变作竞争游戏
You can't make a competition/Out of patient care.
没有竞争 我们还是单细胞有机体呢
Without competition,We'd/still be Single-cell organisms.
- 我能走了吗?/- 等我吼完再说
- Can I go now?/- Not until After the yelling.
他有什么病?
What's wrong with him?
我派了七个最好使的脑子在琢磨/还有三个脑子特殊...
I have seven Of the finest minds on/it.Along with three very special...
如果你不知道答案 你不会这么做
you wouldn't be doing/this,Unless you already knew...
如果我告诉你 你就会告诉他们/游戏就结束了
uh-uh.I tell you,You/tell them.Game's over.
如果你知道 你就该去治疗
If you know,You are obligated to treat.
是这样么 我不确定
Well,then in that case,I don't know.
怎么会有人...
Why would a guy...
主动把金属刺进电插座?
Voluntarily shove A metal/object Into an electrical socket?
我正在慢慢接近答案
I'm getting closer and/closer To knowing the answer.
如果我结束这个游戏会怎样?
What would happen If/i shut down this game?
我把他们都炒了 再雇40个新应聘者/重新开始游戏
I'd fire them all,Hire 40 new Fellowship/applicants,Start the game All over again.
你确实知道他得什么病 对吧?
You do know what's Wrong with him,right?
如果我不知道 那也太不负责任了吧?
Oh,it'd be pretty irresponsible/If I didn't,Wouldn't it?
- 抗生素没有用/- 军团杆菌能解释肺部问题和高烧...
- antibiotics aren't working./- legionella could explain  the lungs,the fever...
如果她得了军团杆菌 就会有低钠症状
If she had legionella,She'd/have low sodium.
关于她个人我们知道什么?
What can you tell me About her?
她喜欢身体冲浪
She likes body surfing.
也许在琼斯海滩游泳时感染了病毒
Maybe picked up a virus/Swimming off jones beach.
但她都没有力气完成填字游戏了
But she doesn't even Have the energy/To finish her Crossword anymore.
- 她男朋友说.../- 就是这个
- Her boyfriend said.../- That's it.
- 什么?/- 视觉模糊
- What is?/- Blurry vision.
你从哪里得出视觉模糊...
How do you get Blurry vision from...
填字游戏是她为了对抗无聊 每天必做的/不会因为无聊而终止
You don't stop a daily ritual That/cures boredom Because you're bored.
她不做填字游戏 是因为看不清楚
She stopped doing Her crossword puzzle/Because she's having A hard time reading it.
什么引起发热 肺积水和视觉模糊?
what causes fever,boggy/lungs And blurry vision?
真菌
Fungal.
曲霉菌解释了肺炎和发烧
Aspergillus would explain The/pneumonia,which explains the fever.
给她用两性霉素
Start her on amphotericin.
伙计们 干得好
hey,guys?Great job.
如果想结果自己
If you're gonna try/To take yourself out,
为什么选触电? 可以饮弹 跳楼...
Why choose electricity?You eat/a bullet,Jump off a building...
顺便说下 我喜欢团队概念
I love the team thing,By the way.
你可以活埋在cuddy的乳沟里
Bury yourself alive In cuddy's cleavage.
团队协作分工 为了集体利益努力
Teamwork,collaboration,All/for the greater good.
这也许只是看起来像是自杀/却不是真的想死
It could have been A suicidal/gesture,As opposed To an actual attempt.
事实上 西班牙的雨不都落在平原上/(引自电影中的歌曲名)
Interestingly,The rain in spain Doesn't/actually fall In the plain all that much.
但谁会仅仅为了引起注意/让内脏遭受电击烘烤?
But who puts their internal Organs/on a skillet Just to get attention?
去问他
Go ask him.
那就是作弊了
That would be cheating.
- 有诊断结果了吗?/- 出去
- Got a diagnosis yet?/- Get out of here.
- 拿到粪便样本了吗?/- 你怎么会知道?
- Got a stool sample yet?/- How could you know?
我问了一个护士 挺聪明的 不是吗?
Oh,i talked to a/nurse.Pretty brilliant,huh?
我给你们支一招 他以前的手下教的/House会喜欢的
i give you a move  House will love,straight/from one Of his former fellows,
- 你们让我加入/- 太迟了
- And you let me join your team./- you're too late.
我们已经有了结果
We already have our diagnosis.
他撒谎是为了让你走开 我也希望你走开
He's lying because He wants/you to go away.So do i.
我们怎么知道你不是双面间谍?
How do we know you're/not A double agent?
弄清我们想什么 再回到女队去?
to find out  what we're/thinking,Then go back to the women?
因为我才不在乎你们想什么
Because I don't care/What you're thinking.
想知道为什么我要来这队?/因为你们是笨蛋
You wanna know why I want to be/on your team?Because you're idiots.
如果我能让女队出局 我就赢了
if I can get the women  out/of the competition,I'm in.
你们中有两个也赢了
And so are two of you.
那么...那高招是什么?
So...what's the big move?
叫异体接种诊断法 让这些虫子咬你
It's called xenodiagnosis.We/let this bugs bite you,
然后我们检测它们粪便里的寄生虫
And then we test their/feces For parasites.
你们为什么不检测我的粪便?
Why can't you Test my feces?
因为一小时来 你都在喝氧化镁乳液/(致泻剂)
Because you've been Chugging milk/of magnesia For the past hour.
你吃进很多 什么都没排出
You have a lot going in/And nothing coming out.
事实上检测虫子的粪便比测你的更准确
testing the bugs' feces Is actually/more accurate Than testing yours.
草垛越小 越容易找针
Smaller haystack,Easier/to find the needle.
你还好吗? 拿开那些虫子
You okay?Get the bugs off.
- 把虫子从他身上拿开!/- 测试还没好
- Get the bugs off him!/- Test isn't done.
他噎住了!
He's choking!
x光片显示肺部有斑块状浸润
patchy infiltrates  on the x-ray.
用胸部物理治疗和氧气疗法/病人已经好转 可以维持呼吸
patient improved  with chest pt and/oxygen,consistent with aspiration.
现在多了一个症状要解释
So now we have Another/symptom to explain.
为什么他的喉咙把他的肺当胃?
Why does his throat think/His lungs are his stomach?
为什么你们的喉咙都紧闭不语?
And why are your throats Closing up?
我们不该分个房间吗?
Shouldn't we be In separate rooms?
难道我会一大清早搞两次鉴别诊断?
You think I'm gonna run Two/differentials This time in the morning?
- 坏脾气 你先来/- 我脾气不坏
- Grumpy,you're first./- I'm not grumpy.
我这么叫你 你就是
Oh,why would I call/you that If you weren't?
这是个不同寻常的组合
It's an unusual Combination.
不寻常等于外来的 等于外国的
Unusual equals exotic,Equals foreign.
应该和他的泰国之行有关
Has to be connected To/his trip to thailand.
你在海外行医?
You practice medicine overseas?
我曾在无国界医师组织工作8年
I was with doctors without/Borders for eight years.
- 我猜对了!/- 这都在我的档案里
- Ta da!/- It's in my file.
虽知David Blaine(街头魔术师)/把红心6藏在啤酒瓶里 却仍令人赞叹
david blaine Hides the six of hearts/In a beer bottle,It's still impressive.
- 你喜欢异国风情 为什么来这儿?/- 我想要这份工作
- you like exotic.Why are you here?/- I want this job.
- 父母生病?/- 不是
- parents sick?/- No.
- 我只是.../- 这不是你想要的工作
- I just.../- This is not the job you want.
你想要的是这个地区的工作 你订婚了?
This is the job In the zip/code you want.You engaged?
- 是的/- 又猜对了!
- Yes./- Ta da!
我就不能长大成人 改变一下人生重心吗?
am I not allowed to grow/up And change my priorities?
你当然可以 可人们通常不这么做
You're allowed to,People usually don't.
这不是新症状 我们的病人有脊髓性肌萎缩症
This is not a new symptom.Our/patient Has spinal muscular atrophy.
记录有吞咽困难 噎住不是新症状
He has documented Trouble/swallowing.The choking's not new.
虽不是新症状 那是什么引起了旧症状?
so it's nothing's/new.What caused the old?
粪圆属虫能解释昏倒
Strongyloides worms/Explain the fainting.
- 我们已经治疗.../- 那他好了么 女队...谁...
- We already treated.../- So he's all better,Woman...Who...
- 13号/- 至少没有变差
- thirteen./- Hasn't got any worse.
酒鬼的女儿 行事不该这么被动保守
it's a pretty passive approach/For the daughter Of an alcoholic.
又猜错了
Wrong again.
可以对他施加些压力 把他放在倾斜床上
we could stress  his/system.Put him on a tilt table.
如果他保持清醒/说明诊断是对的 我们赢
if he stays conscious,means we/made The right diagnosis,And we win.
那你们为什么还不开始?
Then why haven't you?
六对四
Six against four.
一个男的要去加入女队
One of the men's gonna have/To join the women's team.
另一方面 男队里有一个不是真的医生
On the other hand,One of the/men Isn't an actual doctor.
我想这样也算公平
So,i guess it's pretty fair.
男士们 你们在受罚席上
Men,you're in the penalty box.
谁不是医生?
Uh,who's not the doctor?
我很高兴你问起这个
I'm glad you asked about that.
我惩罚你们的原因是时间管理
reason I'm penalizing/you Is time management.
在诊断学中 你永远在和时间赛跑
In diagnostics,you're always/Working against the clock.
女队想出一个理论 她们治疗乐病人
the women came up with a theory/and they treated the patient.
而你们只是坐在实验室/巴望着由一堆盲目的测试得出理论
you guys just sat around  in a lab,hoping a/series of blind tests would give you a theory.
你们浪费了病人的时间
You wasted the patient's time.
那我就浪费你们的时间
Now I'm gonna waste yours.
她的牙龈变黄了
Her gums are turning yellow.
不管是什么病菌 现在已进入肝脏了
Whatever it is,It's in her liver now.
真菌可引发上述所有症状
Fungal fit perfectly.
我们错了
We were wrong.
没找到正解前 我们都在犯错
We're gonna keep being/wrong,Until we're right.
可是她等不起了
Or till she dies.
行 这话太有启发性了
Yeah,that was very helpful.
人总有一死 还用你们来告诉我吗?
Need a team to tell me We're mortals.
对不起 你说的有道理
Look, I'm sorry.You're right.
我们处理的是生死攸关的大事/不时警醒一下是必要的
It doesn't hurt to be reminded That/we're dealing With real stakes here.
肝衰竭很严重 但也是条线索
Liver failure is a bad/thing,But it's also a clue.
这线索说明了什么?
What does it tell us?
我不能让你走 我觉得你还有自杀倾向
I can't let you leave.I/think you're still suicidal.
我没打算自寻死路
I wasn't trying to off myself.
是啊 你只想干掉那堵墙
No,that's right.You were/just trying To kill a wall.
我勾上这个框 (你就得进精神病院)/ 你的室友会是基督和疯子Mcloonybin
I check this box,And your next roommates/Are gonna be jesus And crazy mcloonybin.
那家伙脑子烧得厉害了
That guy never had a chance.
听起来太愚蠢了
It's gonna sound stupid.
你突然害羞了?
Suddenly you're shy?
你还在我面前大便失禁呢
You pooped your pants In front of me.
这是死亡前的恶心副作用之一
It's one of the nasty/Side effects of dying.
上周六 我出了次车祸
Last saturday,i got In a car crash.
醉醺醺的司机违章闯道 把我撞个正着
A drunk driver came over/The line and hit me head on.
就像慢动作一样
It was like slow motion.
我看到车前灯...
I saw these headlights,And...
还看到...
I saw...
急救人员说 理论上讲我死了97秒
The paramedics said I was/technically dead For 97 seconds.
这是我一生中最美妙的97秒
It was the best 97 seconds Of my life.
这可以解释 你缺氧的脑子当时要罢工了
Okay,here's what happened.Your/oxygen-deprived brain was shutting down.
分泌出大量的内啡呔和色胺
A flood of endorphins/And serotonin was released
就是这个导致你产生了幻觉
And it's what gave you The visions.
不 相信我 不是化学分泌物的作用
no.Believe me.It wasn't chemicals.
我试过所有的致幻药
I've done every/hallucinogenic  there is.
这感受要强烈多了
This was way bigger than that.
这种感受
There's something out there.
太不可思议了
Something more.
- 能把刀还给我吗?/- 不行
- Hey,can I have My knife back?/- No.
- 究竟哪个不是医生?/- House说过我们不能讲话
- Who the hell Isn't a doctor?/- House said we can't talk.
他是说我们不能讨论这个病例
He meant we can't talk About the case.
House在把我们当猴耍
House is just Jerking us around.
- 他就爱干这样的事/- 你不好奇吗?
- It's what he does./-You're not curious?
你不好奇只有一个原因
only one reason You wouldn't be curious.
我们应该讨论病例
We should talk about the case.
他是教训我们不该浪费时间/所以我们不该再虚耗光阴了
He's punishing us For wasting time.Maybe/we shouldn't be Wasting this time.
关上门 你会让我们全被炒鱿鱼的
Close that door.You're/gonna get us all fired.
得找出晕厥和吞咽困难的联系
We need to find a link Between/fainting And trouble swallowing.
得弄清楚究竟是吞咽不利症/还是完全性食管失弛缓症
We need to know If it's/dysphagia Or full blown achalasia.
副神经节瘤
Paraganglioma.
他肚子里长个瘤子怎么可能导致...
How would a neoplastic growth/In his abdomen explain...
不在肚子里 在脖子里/颈动脉瘤会导致吞咽困难
Not his abdomen,In his neck.A carotid/body tumor Causes trouble swallowing.
食物压迫迷走神经从而导致晕厥
food presses against  the vagus/nerve,And causes the fainting.
如果这家伙得了癌症 我们就能保住饭碗?
So if this guy has cancer,We/get to keep our jobs?
他要是没病 我们就全都被开除?
If he's healthy,We're fired?
得做个CT核实一下
We need a ct to prove it.
祈祷我们在这傻坐的时候/女队还没弄明白
we need the women not to figure/it out   while we're sitting here.
House的电脑有内置麦克风摄像头吗?
And does House's computer/Have a built-in microphone?
实验性治疗存在一定的毒副作用
there is a potential  toxicity/In the experimental treatment.
当我没来过
I was never here.
呈60度角晃动时 血压保持稳定
Blood pressure's remaining/Stable through 60 degrees.
心电图无停顿 无恶心作呕反应
No pauses on his ekg,No nausea.
我们的治疗生效了
Our treatment worked.
- 我需要病患/- 晕厥症治好了 Amber 已经结束了
- I need our patient./- Syncope's cured,amber.It's over.
很明显这系统你们没使用到位
You obviously haven't stressed/The system hard enough.
你把角度再调大点 是人都会晕过去了
You crank it up high/enough,Anyone will pass out.
太爽了
This is incredible.
40年来我都没颠得这么开心过了
This is the most I've moved in 40 years.
倾斜测试表明病患的心电图/心率脉搏维持正常 尽管...
The tilt table test Showed that the patient's/ekg,Bpm pulse remained Normal despite...
你是谁? 13号吗?
Who are you,thirteen?
档案里有我的名字
My name's in the file.
你不正面回答问题这一事实/能比直接回答说明更多问题
Fact that you don't answer my questions tells me more about/you Than answers could.
胡扯
No,it doesn't.
- 把晃动角度增大到95度.../- 你不觉得拒绝回答耐人寻味吗?
- We turned the thing Up to 95 degrees... - You/don't think that Non-answers tell me anything?
没错 可正面回答揭示更多/不然就不叫"答案"了?
Sure,just not as much As actual/answers.That's why they're called Answers.
- 说明你有所隐瞒/- 说明我不想让你一览无余
- Tells me you're hiding Something./- Tells you I'm hiding everything.
说明你有事非得隐瞒不可/在土耳其坐过牢? 参演同性恋色情片?
Tells me you got something Worth/hiding.Is it turkish prison?Gay porn?
你杀过人 就因为他问了太多问题?
You killed a man,Just because/he was asking Too many questions?
- 能让我做完病患报告吗?/- 不用了
- Can I finish reporting On the patient?/- No need.
过一个小时 我再来见你/我该去装神弄鬼了
I'll see you In an hour or so./Got to set some stuff up.
感谢诸位前来参加...
Thank you all for coming...
部落议会
To tribal council.
汝等中一员吾可信任者 谓之大爱/(: HBO新剧 以摩门教为背景)
A man of your integrity I/feel I can trust.Big love.
我这么叫你 不是因为你是摩门教徒
and I don't call you that/Because you're a mormon.
你们队里还有一个人呢?
Where's your team's sixth man?
她离队了 违反了规则
she went rogue.Broke the rules.
你同样有罪 所以无权第一个拿石头砸她/(源自圣经约翰福音)
You also sinned.You have no/right To cast the first stone.
无神论者无权引用圣经
And atheists have no/right To quote scripture.
我规定了不能讲话
The rules said no talking.
- 我跟他们说了不要讲话/- 也是大声说话
- I told them not to talk./- Out loud.
我们在试图挽救人的生命
We were trying To save a man's life.
可惜仅仅是"试图"/倾斜测试证实你们错了
Key word being "trying."Tilt table/test confirmed That you guys were wrong.
你们被开除了
You're fired.
浪子回头了(圣经故事)/你也被开除了
Ah,the prodigal son/returneth.You're also fired.
我们之前认为病患食道里长有肿瘤
We thought there was a tumor/on the patient's esophagus.
部位是对的 可诊断错了
We were right About the/area,Wrong about the diagnosis.
结果是食道僵直了 他得了硬皮症
turns out the esophagus  is just/straightening.It's scleroderma.
可解释晕厥和窒息两种症状/需使用类固醇治疗
Explains the syncope And the/choking.He needs steroids.
- 你做了CT扫描?/- 当然
- you did a ct scan?/- Obviously.
在被证明错了之后还去做?
After you were already Proven wrong?
干得不错
Good for you.
很可惜你还是错了
It's too bad you're wrong.
僵直是由衰弱引起的 而不是硬皮症
Straightening Indicates/weakening,not hardening.
脊髓性肌萎缩症是衰弱的原因
sma explains the weakening.
类圆线虫属感染则导致了其他症状
Strongyloides infection/Explains everything else.
女士们 你们很荣幸/可以去给病患插上喂食管
You ladies have the honor To/give the patient A feeding tube,
批准其出院 然后明天继续上班
discharge him,and show/up  for work tomorrow.
剩下的各位 你们太让人失望了
The rest of you,You're a disappointment.
让我都愧为男同胞了
You make me Want to stop dangling.
这是我一生中最棒的两个星期
It was the best Two weeks of my life.
看来你会是我最怀念的人 老头骗子
I think I will miss you  Most of/all,Ridiculously old fraud.
你觉得House会不会弄错了?
Do you think House Could be wrong?
我还以为他把你开除了呢
I thought he fired you.
没有 他把男的都开除了
No.He fired the men.
我觉得他没错
I don't think He's wrong.
如果他错了 我该怎么去证明呢?
If he is, How would I prove it?
我刚才说了觉得他没错
I just said I don't think he is.
仅仅凭感觉是不够的
Well,thinking Isn't good enough.
你得做个血检来测试抗着丝点抗体
You have to run a blood test/For anticentromere antibodies.
你能帮我去实验室做测试吗?
Would you mind Running the labs?
你不行
You can't.
我是不行 不过...
Well,i can,but...
不行 没得商量
No.I was making a statement.
你已经被开除了 所以无权使用实验室
You've been fired, So you no/longer have Lab privileges.
你来这不是咨询意见
You weren't coming here For advice,
你来是想骗我帮你 好保住饭碗
You were coming here To con/a favor to save your job.
我爱莫能助
Sorry.
我不再为他工作了/可他仍有办法把我的生活弄得一团糟
I'm not working For him anymore, But/he can still Make my life miserable.
现在你有机会把他的生活弄得一团糟了
And you have a chance To/make his life miserable.
真是出言不逊啊
I'm insulted.
你算准Cameron仁慈 利用了她
You con cameron By/appealing To her humanity.
我不过是说了她想听的话
I told her What she wanted to hear.
现在你说我想听的话
And you told me What you/thought I wanted to hear.
相比之下 研究你的心态更有趣些/这也算得上是恭维
If it's any consolation, I think/your motives Are more interesting.
真不敢相信他居然开除了你
I cannot believe He fired you.
去给病患抽血
Go draw his blood.
我忙完了去实验室找你
I'll meet you in the/lab When I'm done here.
看样子你没找到肿瘤
Guess you didn't find Your tumor.
其他医生说你已经没事了?
The other doctors Tell/you that you were fine?
是的
Yeah.
他们说不过是我的病情发展了
They said it was just/My disease getting worse.
你不断向疾病妥协
You come to terms With this disease.
它就在那
You know it's there.
虎视眈眈
you know it's waiting.
时不时地...
and every now and again...
夺走一些东西
It takes something away.
让我瘫痪
Took my walking.
丧失尊严
Took my modesty.
现在它要夺走我最后的快乐了
Now it's taking One/of my last pleasures.
还有一种可能性
Well,there's an outside shot
进食问题可能不是由脊髓肌肉萎缩症引发
That something other Than the/sma's causing Your eating problems.
如果是这样 我们就能治好它
And if it is, We can fix it.
不需要喂食导管
and remove that tube.
这是我的血吗?
Is that my blood?
是绿色的
It's green.
怎么回事?
What does that mean?
说明我不会被开除了
It means I'm not fired.
他是瓦肯人吗?(星舰奇航中的外星人)
Is he a vulcan?
倘若不是 尼摩伊为什么流绿血呢?/(尼摩伊演星舰中外星科学家 血液含铜)
If no,what makes nimoy Bleed green?
开除我们的决定正式解除了么?
Are we officially Unfired?
怎么证明/绿血不是她弄虚作假造出来的?
How do we know she didn't/Fake the green blood?
因为那样就太蠢了 虽然她爱算计
Because that would be stupid.And/while she May be manipulative,
无视规矩 浅薄...
Borderline evil, Shallow...
他们听懂了
They get it.
我并不蠢
I'm not stupid.
CT你用的什么对比液?
what contrast did you use for the ct?
离子型造影剂
Icm.
他的肾脏衰竭了
His kidneys aren't working.
无法过滤对比液 在离子型造影剂中呈绿色
they didn't filter the/contrast, Which in icm is green.
10分
Ten points.
好 把肾衰竭列入症状之一
Okay,let's add Kidney failure/To our list of symptoms.
加分意义何在?
what are these points?
你根据这个来决定开除谁吗?
Is that how you're deciding Who to fire?
谁再问我打算开除谁/我就打算开除了他
I'm gonna fire The next person/who asks me Who I'm going to fire.
现在又是得分制了?
Now we're on the point system?
男队女队的比赛怎么办?
What happened to men Against women?
别管什么比赛了
Forget the game.
别管比赛是什么意思?
What do you mean Forget the game?
意思就是别管TMD的比赛了!
I mean forget the damn game!
这家伙肾衰竭了
The guy's kidneys are failing.
我们得确诊...
We need to diagnose exactly...
我们不是一直在会诊吗?
I thought we Were diagnosing.
那是你们在会诊 现在加上我
You were diagnosing.Now I am too.
我本以为13号关于类圆线虫属感染的诊断是正确的
I thought that thirteen Was/right about the strongyloides.
明显我错了
I was obviously wrong.
好 肾衰竭 呼吸 晕厥 开始
Okay,kidney failure,/Aspiration,fainting,go.
肾衰竭可能是由革兰氏阴性菌引起的
kidney failure could be the/result Of a gram negative bacteria.
病患长期导尿管
Our patient wears A catheter full time.
极有可能导致细菌感染
it virtually guarantees/Bacterial infection.
进而感染到肾脏
Which could have migrated/Up to his kidneys.
感染令其原本就虚弱的身体更不堪重负/脊髓肌肉萎缩症也进一步恶化
Infection stresses His already/weakened system, Makes his sma worse.
这可解释吞咽困难和晕厥两种症状
That explains the choking And fainting.
静脉注射氨苄青霉素
Put him on An iv amp and gent.
我们队关于硬皮症的诊断依然成立
our team's scleroderma/diagnosis still holds.
测试结果为阴性是因为血样被对比液污染了
The tests could Have been negative Because/the blood Was tainted with contrast.
做皮肤活检
Do a skin biopsy.
同时测试淋巴腺加以核实
Get a side of lymph node To confirm.
我本可以让你被炒鱿鱼的
i could have you fired.
你已经炒我鱿鱼了
You already had me fired.
仅仅是证明一下我可以
Just proves than I can.
男队错了吗?
And were the men wrong?
没有
No.
- 这也无法改变事实.../- 你干嘛冲我吼?
- It doesn't change the fact.../- Why are you yelling at me?
因为你为非本院医生做测试...
Because performing tests For someone/who is not a doctor In this hospital...
你心烦受挫了
You're frustrated.
需要帮忙 我随叫随到/可如果只想找人出气 恕不奉陪
You want help?I'm here.If you/just need to vent, Leave a message.
他这样 我更喜欢了
I like him better like this.
你呢?
You?
病患发展为肺炎
Patient developed Pneumonia.
肺部迅速积水
His lungs are filling fast.
我们给他用了抗生素 无效
We started him on antibiotics.Nothing.
- 我们队错了/- 你来是想说...?
- We were wrong./- And you're here to say...?
我们队也错了/他没得硬皮症
We were wrong too.He/doesn't have scleroderma.
活检显示无纤维性?
Biopsy revealed No fibrotic changes.
颈部淋巴腺上有黑色斑点
Cervical lymph node Has black flecks.
小规模的坏疸 无大碍
Small areas of necrosis.It's nothing.
你说无大碍,我说是癌症
You say nothing.I say cancer.
结论突然就跳到癌症 未免激进
It's a bit of a stretch/To jump right to cancer.
并不激进/广谱抗生素无效 所以不是细菌引起的
I'm not jumping.Broad specs haven't/worked, So it's not bacterial.
在治疗后肝脏还是衰竭 说明不是真菌引起的
Failing liver Despite treatment/Suggests it's not fungal.
她的高乳酸性酸中毒则表明/是间变性大细胞性淋巴瘤引起的
And her high lactic acidosis Points/towards anaplastic Large cell lymphoma.
也有可能是感染造成的/治疗起来更容易 也更安全
Also suggests Infection, Which is/a lot easier And safer to treat.
大细胞淋巴瘤发作起来很迅猛
Large cell lymphoma Is/incredibly aggressive.
如果我们按步就搬/她一周内就可能死亡
She'll be dead in a week/If we follow the textbooks.
如果仅仅是感染 你却采取放射治疗/她一天内就可能死亡
Unless it's infection, In which case You/radiate her And she'll be dead In a day.
你对此是有体会的
I know you have some/experience With that.
我以前见过医生这么做
I've seen doctors Do this before.
总是回想以前的过错
Go back to the scene Of the crime.
以为如果这次做对了/就能清洗过往的罪过
If you're right this time, You/purge yourself Of past ghosts.
我明白这不合规程/可我觉得这可能性更大...
I know it's contrary To protocol,/But I think it's more likely...
困扰我们的往事有意义
Ghosts are there For a reason.
能避免重蹈覆辙
So you don't make The/same mistake twice.
换上第三代的先锋霉素
Switch over to/third-generation Cephalosporin.
你要摘除他的眼球?
You want to remove his eye?
谁告诉你的?
Who told you?
你定了手术室
You booked the o.r.
没错
Good.
走路你可走不赢我
You can't beat me In a foot race.
我还以为我们在跳舞呢
I thought We were dancing.
颈部淋巴腺就像个垃圾堆
Cervical lymph node Is a garbage dump.
非常小的垃圾堆
Very small one.
只有一辆垃圾车运送一户人家的垃圾
Just one truck comes in And/only comes from one home.
阿尔·戈尔(美国前副总统)会给吓坏的/这户人家...
Al gore would be Appalled.The home...
源头就是右眼 我明白
The home is the right eye.I get it.
- 做个活检/- 这不正要去么
- Do a biopsy./- on my way.
你不会去做活检的
You're not doing A biopsy.
你定的手术是眼眶内容物剜出术
You ordered An orbital exenteration.
没错,因为我不想就切除那么一点点做活检
Right.Because I don't want/To remove A little tiny piece,
然后坐在办公室里核实我已经了解的情况
Sit in the lab And confirm/What I already know,
与此同时/我的病人则被自己的体液给淹死了
While my patient/drowns In his own fluid.
不过你要希望我去做活检的话 /我一定照办
But if you want me/to, I absolutely will.
肺炎有多严重?
How advanced Is the pneumonia?
已经深到大学水平了
It's taking college courses.
Wilson 我要把个跛子的眼睛挖出来
Hey,wilson, I'm gonna cut/Some cripple's eye out.
想观看吗?
Wanna come watch?
巧得很
Good times.
我们可以走了?
We good to go?
我以为黑素瘤是皮肤癌
I thought melanoma Was skin cancer.
严格说来 是色素细胞癌
Technically it's cancer/Of the pigment cells.
就是决定你虹膜颜色的细胞
The same cells that/give Your iris its color.
癌?
cancer?
为什么不呢? 否则上帝还能赐予我什么?
Why not?What else can god throw at me?
冰雹 蝗虫 击杀所有头生的事物/
Hail,locusts, Smiting of the first born.
就看你是不是作恶多端
Of course it all depends/On how evil you've been.
House...
如果是癌 就会全身扩散 对吗?
If it's cancer,it's/spread Everywhere,right?
所以癌细胞进入了我的肺 我的肾?
so it's in my lungs, My kidneys?
通过移除眼睛 摘除原发性瘤
There is a chance By removing/the eye, Get the primary tumor,
加上三次放射疗程 你还有机会能...
and three courses of/radiation, That could...
能...怎么样?
could...what?
活上几个月? 几年?
few months?Years?
可能是几个月
More likely months.
其他医生有乐观些的诊断吗?
Any of your other doctors/Have any cheerier diagnoses?
别的诊断都是错的 这就是答案
if they do,they're/wrong.This is the answer.
你只有这条路可走
It's the only way To help you.
我已经不能走
I already Can't walk.
不能吃
I can't eat.
你说我要在这张床上度过余生
You're telling me That the/rest of my life Is in this bed,
不停呕吐 受疼痛折磨?
Puking and in pain?
可以帮你减轻疼痛
We can manage the pain.
我宁愿一死了之
I'd rather just Get this over with.
在这一无是处的躯壳里/我已经被困太久
I've been trapped in this/Useless body long enough.
能最后解脱反而是好事
It'd be nice To finally get out.
解脱后去哪儿?
Get out and go where?
你以为自己会萌生翅膀
you think you're gonna sprout wings,
和其他天使一起到处翱翔?
and start flying around/with the other angels?
别白痴了 人生没有来世 只有此生
Don't be an idiot.There is/no after, There's just this.
House!
你就不能让个垂死之人/从信仰中寻求慰藉吗?
You can't let a dying man/Take solace in his beliefs?
他的信仰太愚蠢
His beliefs Are stupid.
人人都撒谎
Everybody lies.
理由有好有坏
Some for good reason, Some for bad,
要为这撒谎 这理由也太玄妙了
This would have been A/fantastic reason to lie.
嗨 Grey House
Hi,greg House.
为什么不让他生活在童话里呢?
Why can't you just Let/him have his fairy tale?
如果幻想沙滩 幻想爱人
If it gives him comfort/To imagine beaches,
幻想脱离轮骑的生活能带给他安慰...
And loved ones,and life/outside A wheel chair...
幻想里有72个处女吗?/(伊斯兰教里 殉道者可上天堂 得72处女)
Are there 72 virgins too?
他的生命到头了
It's over.
没几天可活了 也许就几个小时
He's got days, Maybe hours left.
他带着宁静的笑容迎接死亡/你又苦恼什么?
What pain does it cause you If he/spends that time With a peaceful smile?
让他充满恐惧和忧虑
What sick pleasure do you/get In making damn sure
能让你得到什么变态的满足?
He's filled With fear and dread?
他不该在谎言的基础上做决定
He shouldn't be making A/decision based on a lie.
悲惨好过一无所有
Misery's better than nothing.
你不知道死亡那头是否一无所有
You don't know there's nothing.
你又没经历过
You haven't been there.
老天爷 我烦透这种争吵了
Oh,god.I am tired Of that argument.
我不用去底特律 就知道那里臭哄哄
I don't have to go To detroit/To know that it smells.
难道底特律和来生是一码事?
Yes,detroit, The afterlife.Same thing.
歌曲: Not As We/歌手: Alanis Morissette
Song: Not As We/Singer: Alanis Morissette
视觉模糊
blurry vision
你呼吸不到足够的氧气
You're not getting Enough oxygen,
所以我们要把管子直接插进你肺里
So we're inserting A tube/Directly Into your lungs.
好抽取多余的肺液
It should help us drain/Some of this excess fluid.
会有点不舒服
It should make you A/little more comfortable.
血氧饱和度还在下降
sats are still dropping.
肺液很干净
fluid's clear.
如果是癌 里面应该有血
If this was cancer,/There should be blood.
呼叫House
Call House.
他刚呼我
He just paged me.
House医生
dctor House
也许...
Maybe it was...
只是意外
Just an accident.
这不是意外
It wasn't an accident.
你以为虚无主义占据了他的思想?/他想自杀?
You think his nihilism Got the best/of him?He tried to kill himself?
他传呼了我
He paged me.
- 传呼你?/- 为什么是你?
- Paged you?/- Why you?
- 我猜是因为.../- 别随便瞎猜
- I assume because.../- don't assume anything.
别掉陷阱里去
Don't fall into that trap.
他还好吗?
Is he okay?
手部烧伤挺严重
Burned his hand pretty good.
他心跳停止近一分钟
His heart stopped For nearly a minute.
医护人员让它又重新跳动了起来
Your cohort managed to restart it.
可他...还没恢复意识
but he...Has not regained consciousness.
所以...
so...
既然大家都来了/我们就谈谈你的现行病人
Since I have you all here, We should/probably talk About your actual patient.
肺液干净表明多半不是癌
clear fluid from the lungs indicates/that it's probably Not cancer.
所以我们最好能提出新的想法
So it would be nice If we/could come up With a new idea.
你是白痴
You're an idiot.
几乎杀死自己
you nearly killed yourself.
正有此意
That was the whole idea.
你想自杀?
You wanted to kill yourself?
我想濒临死亡
I wanted to nearly kill myself.
- 他...好些了吗?/- 不
- is he...Better?/- no.
可他没得癌症
But he doesn't have cancer.
我们认为也许是嗜酸球性肺炎
We think it might be/Eosinophilic pneumonia.
也许你不想死 但对生活又很麻木
Maybe you didn't wanna die, But/you didn't care If you lived.
是你坚持 我得自己经历一下死亡
You insisted that i/needed To see for myself.
- 他出院了吗?/- 不 他要死了
- Was he discharged?/- No.He's dying.
你都经历两次濒死体验了
You've already had Two/near death experiences.
那个人没有
Not that guy.
那个拿着小刀 遭遇车祸的家伙
The guy in the car/accident, With the knife.
我...得跟他谈谈
I...i need to talk to him.
他一小时前死了
He died Almost an hour ago.
遭受大内伤后没几天 就再触电
Apparently it's bad/To electrocute yourself
后果不堪设想
Within days of suffering/Massive internal injuries.
你为什么要跟他谈?
Why did you need To talk to him?
你看到什么了吗?
Did you see something?
嗜酸球性肺炎
Eosinophilic pneumonia.
House? 你看到了什么?
House?What did you see?
没什么
Nothing.
谁想出来的?
Whose idea was that?
Brennan 你是不想讨论 还是没有...
Brennan.Nothing you don't Want/to talk about it, Or nothing...
谁是Brennan?
Which one is brennan?
那个老头子吗?
Is he the ridiculously Old guy?
House 你得讲出来
House,you got to talk About this.
如果病情来势汹汹/也许类固醇已经无效了
If it's aggressive enough, It/might have gotten Past the steroids.
给他用环磷酰胺
Start him on cyclophosamide.
我已经给他用药了
i already did.
只是来看看你的伤
Just looking at you hurts.
我给你多开些止痛药
I'm gonna order up Some extra pain meds.
我爱你
I love you.
这药多久能起作用?
How fast will this work?
新药几分钟就能起作用? 坚持一下
New meds should start Helping/in minutes,okay?Hang in there.
采液管满了 我得换掉它
Vacutainer's full.I need to replace it.
我不...我不认为...
I don't... I don't think...
药起作用了
It's working.
试着放松
Try and relax.
你一定...你一定搞错了
You must...you must be wrong.
别说话
Stop talking.
快点 把胸腔导管插好
Hurry up and get That/chest tube working.
好的 我明白
Okay, I got it.
你能不能...
Could you get...
把Hoover抱过来?
Hoover?
我不能...
I can't...
你能...
can you...
把我手放在...
Put my hand...
他头上吗?
On his head?
没事的 别担心
It's okay.Don't worry.
我不害怕
I'm not scared.
哦 天哪
Oh,god.
死亡时间?
Time of death?
你气色好些了
You're looking better.
Stark死了
Stark's dead.
你要干什么?
What are you doing?
去看病人
Going to see our patient.
他死了
He's dead.
死亡不是诊断
Dead is not a diagnosis.
你真的不该...
You really shouldn't be...
闭嘴 把拐杖给我
Shut up and give me my cane.
我猜我们全被开除了
I assume we're all fired.
我也该把自己开除吗?
Should I fire myself too?
我以为是圆线虫 后来又认为是癌
I thought it was Strongyloides,/Then I thought It was cancer.
- 帮我一把/- 准备好了? 一 二...
- A little help here./- Ready?One,two...
你为什么叫我?
Why did you call me?
因为我要是在Wilson前面撑不住/他就会唠叨个没完
Because if I pooped myself In front/of wilson,I'd never hear The end of it.
为什么不叫别人?
But why not One of the others?
你手里一直拿着手机
You always have That phone in your hand.
我们都有手机 不是这个原因/到底什么原因?
We all have cell phones.That's/not the reason.What is?
如果我死了 你永远别想得到这份工作
If I died, You'd never get the job.
我知道你想这样
I knew you wouldn't let That happen.
难道你认为没人关心你?
You don't think Anybody/else Has any reason to care?
我开始掌握了
Think this is starting/To come back to me.
右 左 再重复
It's right,left, Then repeat.
行了 可以了
Yeah,that works.
我们遗漏了什么?
What did we miss?
如果我们知道 他就不会死了
If we knew, He wouldn't be dead.
就这样? 你就这样放弃了?
That's it?You're just gonna Give up?
不 我们失败了 这事结束了
No,we were defeated.It's over.
病人出现昏厥
Patient presented With syncope.
我们以为是线虫 就给他用了伊维菌素/(抗生素药 主要治线虫病)
We thought it was thread/worms, Gave him ivermectin.
谢谢
Thank you.
他似乎有所好转 直到血液变绿
He seemed better, Till/his blood turned green.
我们能不能先把尸体挪走/再进行纯学术的讨论?
Can we at least Remove the body Before/launching Into a purely academic exercise?
病人对抗生素和类固醇没有反应
Patient didn't respond To/antibiotics or steroids.
你还好吗 孩子?
You okay,boy?
狗怎么了?
What's wrong with the dog?
他死了
He's dead.
只有几种病毒能在人和狗之间传染
There are only A handful of viruses/That can cross Between dogs and humans.
也许跟病毒毫无关系
but they may not be connected at all.
狗老了 我以前见过这种事
the dog was old.I've seen it before.
它们本该老死却坚持活了下来/为的是照顾主人
they hang on way past their normal life/expectancy To take care of their masters.
你看到他服药了吗?
Did you watch him Take the pills?
伊维菌素
The ivermectin.
你亲眼看到病人把药塞嘴里咽下去了吗?
Did you watch the patient Put/them in his mouth And swallow them?
记不清了 我想是吧
I don't know.I think so.
这是什么狗?
What kind of dog is that?
英国牧羊犬
English shepherd.
- 是种牧羊狗 对吧?/- 不完全是
- It's in the collie family, Right?/- Not really.
- 它们都有MDR1基因/- 对
- They share the mdr1 gene./- yeah.
给有MDR耐药基因的狗/服用伊维菌素会怎么样?
What happens When you give a dog/With the mdr1 gene Ivermectin?
不行/这药物用于治疗大多数狗的恶丝虫病
They don't...i mean, It's used/to treat Heartworms in most dogs,
可对牧羊犬 会产生致命反应
but it'd be fatal If the...
看着眼熟吗?
Look familiar?
我认为你上次看到它时
I think the last time You saw it,
上面还没有死狗的牙印
It didn't have that dead/dog's Teeth marks on it.
我把它放在托盘上 好去给他倒水
I just put it on the bed/tray To get him some water.
我刚问你是否看到病人吞药/正确答案是"没有"
When I asked you If you watched the patient/Swallow the pills,The right answer was "no."
把他尸体送到停尸房去
Take his body down To the morgue.
要不是你拿病人当儿戏 他不会死
If you hadn't treated This patient/as a game, He wouldn't be dead.
我感觉好多了 谢谢你
I'm feeling much better, Thank you.
我该同情你?
I'm supposed To show you sympathy?
他死时 他的主治医师正因为
He died while his attending/Was lying on a hospital bed,
把刀子插进墙上插座而躺在病床上
Because he stuck A/knife in a wall socket.
他死是因为有个医生犯错
He died because a doctor Made a mistake.
她是白痴
She was an idiot.
她是你雇的
You employed her.
你该负责任
You're responsible.
Foreman医生
Doctor foreman.
她怎么样?
How's she doing?
烧退了
Fever's gone.
转氨酶AST/ALT比值回到了正常范围
A.s.t.And a.l.t.Are/back Within normal range.
她几天后就能出院了
She should be out of here In a few days.
你胆子可不小
Gutsy call.
谢谢
Thanks.
这不是赞美
It wasn't a compliment.
要是你错了 她这会已经死了
If you were wrong, She'd be dead.
- 我肯定.../- 不 你不肯定 你没法肯定
- I was sure.../- No,you weren't.You couldn't be.
设定规章制度是有原因的
There's a reason We have rules.
如果每个医生都凭直觉行事
If every doctor did Whatever/his gut Told him was right,
死去的人会多得多
We'd have a lot more/Dead bodies to deal with.
这种事不会再发生了
It won't happen again.
不 这种事还会发生
Yes,it will.
因为你已经混淆了 什么是救人命/什么是做对的事
Because you confuse Saving her/life With doing the right thing.
对不起 Foreman医生 你被解雇了
I'm sorry dr.Foreman, You're fired.
病理学家一剖开肺脏 就看到了线虫
As soon as the pathologist Cut into/the lungs,We saw the threadworms.
你认为我把你们组其他人都解雇公平么?
You think it's fair That I fired/all The other members of your team
事实上 你们组的诊断没错
When you guys Actually came/up With the right diagnosis?
我不断地回想那一刻
I keep replaying it In my mind.
我把药放床托盘上时 药是否掉了?
Did I drop the pills When/i put them on the bed tray?
是不是我转身时把药打翻了?
Did I knock them over/When I turned to leave?
你知道他本可以活下来
You know he'd be alive.
他的狗会活下来
His dog would be alive.
我知道
I know.
你迫使我们依据错误的设想行动
You forced us to act/On a false assumption.
我知道
I know.
所有的诊断都是以那一步为基础
Everything we built From that step on...
之后的测试 理论 治疗...
Every test,every theory,/Every treatment...
我知道 别教训我了 你已经解雇我了
I know.Forget the lecturey.***
如果我要炒你 就不会教训你了
If I was gonna fire you, I/wouldn't be giving you The lecture.
我知道你不会重蹈覆辙的
I know you're not gonna let/Anything like this Ever happen again.
明天见
I'll see you tomorrow.
很抱歉我得说 "早告诉你了"
I'm sorry to say "i told you so" .